Today we are going to learn about Binary Digits. Hands up if you've heard of a thing called a bit in a computer. Have you heard of a bit?
今天，我们将学习二进制数。 你们听说过计算机中，一个叫“位”的东西吗？ 听说过的请举手。听说过吗？
A bit comes from binary digits. We take the first letter of binary and add the last bit of digit and we shorten it to bits.
位 (bit) 是二进制数的简称。我们将二进制 (binary) 的首字母和数字 (digit) 的最后一个字母相结合，将二进制数 (binary digit) 缩写为位 (bit)。
Right now we've got five bits standing up here. Let's see what that means.
现在，这里有五位处于站立状态。 大家看看，这意味着什么。
I'm going to give you the number 1, you're going to be a bit that represents 1 dot.
我将给你数字 1， 你将变成一个位，代表 1 个点。
You're going to be a bit that represents 2 dots.
你将变成一个位，代表 2 个点。
What's the next number? Call it out. (4, 3)
下一个数字是什么？大声说出来。（4、3）
Hands up if you think 3. That's our counting system.
认为是 3 的同学，请举手。那是我们的计数系统。
Let's see if you are right with binary. Oh! It's 4.
让我们看看，你们在二进制上对不对。哦不！答案是 4。
What could be the next number? Yes? (6 or 5). It could be 6 or 5. It's actually 8.
下一个数字可能是什么？嗯？（6 或 5）。 它可能是 6 或 5。而实际上它是 8。
What's happening with those numbers? What's the next number Oliver? (16) Is he right?
这些数字有什么规律呢？Oliver，下一个数字是什么？(16) 他回答得对吗？
What's the next number after 16 then? Jacob (32) Oh, what comes after 32?
16 之后又是哪个数字呢？Jacob (32) 哦，那么 32 之后呢？
(136) Could be, what else could it be? Lachlin (64) Is he right? (yes).
(136) 有可能哦，但还可能是什么呢？Lachlin (64) 他对了吗？（是的）。
What's the next number that comes after 64? Thomas (128) After that? Jacob? (256) There we go.
64 之后的数字是什么？Thomas (128) 那之后呢？Jacob？(256) 干得漂亮。
Does anyone know what the next one is? Ben. (512) So when we... What's the next one Jacob?
有谁知道下一个数字是什么吗？Ben。(512)  所以，当我们……下一个数字呢 Jacob？
So with only a few bits we can count up really high, right?
因此，只需要用几个位，我们就可以 数到很大的数字了，对吗？
If we look at this we can count 1, 2, 4, 8, 16 dots.
如果看这个的话，我们可以数到 1、2、4、8、 16 个点。
Let's look at what that means inside a computer. A bit can be on or it can be off. So this bit can be on or it can be off.
让我们看看，在计算机中，它意味着什么。位可能处于开启，也可能处于关闭状态。因此，这个位可能是开启，也可能是关闭。
Now what I want you guys to do is think of a number between 31 and 1. Hands up if you thought of a number. Ben, what number (12).
现在，我想让大家想出 31 和 1 之间的一个数字。想到数字的同学请举手。Ben，什么数字 (12)。
12 What we want to do is look at these dots and show 12 dots in binary. Do we want 16 on or off? (off). Turn off please.
12 现在需要看着这些点，并用二进制的方法表示 12 个点。我们应该开启还是关闭 16 呢？（关闭）。请关闭。
If we are making the number 12 do we want 8 on or off? (on) OK, how many's left over then? (4) Do we want 4 dots on or off? (on).
如果要表示的是数字 12，我们应该开启还是关闭 8 呢？（开启）好的，还剩多少呢？(4) 我们需要开启还是关闭 4 个点呢？（开启）。
What about 2? (off) Why? Why is 2 getting turned off? (Because You've already made 12 with the 8 and 4). So 1 stays on or ...? (off)
2 怎么办？（关闭）为什么？为什么要关闭 2？（因为您已经用 8 和 4 表示 12 了）。因此，1 应该开启还是……？（关闭）
Who can tell me in binary what 12 would be, representing 12? Who wants to have a go? (off, on, on, off, off) Thumbs up if you agree.
谁可以告诉我二进制中 12 是什么，如何表示 12？谁要试着回答一下？（关闭、开启、开启、关闭、关闭）同意的话，请竖起你的大拇指。
What about Elarn, do you want to make, can you guys all turn yourselves back on again,
Elarn 认为如何呢，要表示一下吗？大家都可以先把自己开启了，
Elarn, choose a number that we are going to make. (24) 24 Can you just turn yourself back on please.
Elarn，选一个你想要表示的数字。(24) 24 你可以先把自己开启吗？
For 24 do we want 16 on or off? (on) 8 on or off (on) 4, (off) 2 (off) 1 (off).
为了 24，我们应该开启还是关闭 16？（开启）8 开启 或关闭（开启）4、（关闭）2（关闭）1（关闭）。
Elarn, what is binary for 24 dots? (on, on, off, off, off).
Elarn，24 个点的二进制是怎样的？（开启、开启 关闭、关闭、关闭）。
Could we make the number 1 for me. How would we do that?
大家可以给我表示一下 1 吗？我们应该怎么表示 1？
How would we make the number 1? (black, black, black, black, white) Can you guys make that?
可以如何表示数字 1？（黑色、黑色、黑色、黑色、白色）你们可以做到吗？
Now that you've seen the number 1 is there another number you can think of that would be even lower than 1? Will?
现在，大家都看到数字 1 在那儿了。 你们还能想到比 1 更小的数字吗？Will？
(0) How would you make 0? (turn off the white one).
(0) 你可以如何表示 0？（关闭白色）。
We can make the lowest number zero and the highest number, if you turn on all your cards back on, with five bits, what's the highest number we can represent? Ben? (31) Hands up if you agree with Ben? It is 31.
我们可以表示最小数字零以及 最大数字。如果你们再次把卡片全部开启，在有五位的情况下，我们可以 表示的最大数字是多少？Ben？（31）同意 Ben 的同学请举手？它是 31。
If we can make 31 what's the next card going to be? If I join this and become the sixth bit what's the next number? (32) 32.
如果我们可以表示 31，那么下一张卡片的数字将会是多少？如果我加入其中，成为第六位，下一个数字会是多少？(32) 32。
If I turn on 32 these guys all have to turn (off) off to make 32. If you guys all turn off.
如果我把 32 打开，这些家伙都必须（关闭） 关闭以表示 32。你们可以全部关闭吗？
Let's do some counting and see what happens with the different bits.
让我们做一些计数，看看不同的位 会有什么情况。
We've got zero. What do we need to do to make 1? Yes, give the instructions (turn on 1).
我们得到了零。应该如何表示 1？是的，给出指令（开启 1）。
2, how do we make 2? Tell the people (turn off 1, turn on 2) 3? Lachlin, go (turn 1 on and keep 2 on).
2，我们如何表示 2？告诉大家（关闭 1、开启 2）3？Lachlin，开始吧（开启 1，并保持 2 为开启状态）。
4? (turn 2 and 1 off and turn 4 on) 5? (turn 1 on...) What are you noticing about the first bit?
4？（开启 2，关闭 1，再开启 4）5？（开启 1……） 你注意到第一位有什么情况了吗？
Zander, what are you noticing (it does all the work) It seems to be doing all the work.
Zander，你注意到了哪些情况（它做了 所有工作）。看起来它做了所有工作。
Why does it seem that it is doing all the work? Ben? (you can't make odd numbers without it) Turn on all your bits again.
为什么看起来它似乎做了所有工作？ Ben？（没有它，你无法表示奇数）再次开启你的全部位。
What's the difference between the first bit and all the other bits that you can see?
你看到的第一位和你能看到的其他所有位 有什么区别？
William? (number 1 is the only odd number) It's the only odd number.
William？（数字 1 是仅有的奇数）它是仅有的奇数。
We can represent lots of numbers right? I wonder how we would represent letters?
我们可以表示很多数字，对吗？我想知道，可以如何表示字母？
Turn to the person next to you and come up with any ideas you might have about how to represent letters.
和身旁的小伙伴讨论 你认为可以如何表示字母。
How do you think you might represent a letter?
你认为可以如何表示字母？
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, eyes this way.
5、4、3、2、1，看这边。
Hands up whose got a suggestion as to how we can use these to represent letters. What ideas have you got?
想到该如何使用这些表示字母的同学 请举手。你有什么想法？
(You could have the number represent the letter. 26 could be Z and A could be 1) 26 could be Z, A could be 1, what would B be then? Jacob?
（可以用数字表示字母。26 可以表示 Z，A 可以表示 1）26 可以表示 Z，A 可以表示 1，那么 B 是什么呢？Jacob？
(2), what would C be (3), What would D be? (4), E? (5). I think you've got the hang of it.
(2)，C 是什么呢 (3)，那么 D 呢？(4)，E？(5)。我觉得你们已经理解相关的内容了。
I wonder if you can work out what I'm sending you. I'm going to send you a message.
我想知道，你们是否清楚我给你们发的 是什么。我将给你们发一条消息。
Black, white, black, black, black. What number is that? (8).
黑色、白色、黑色、黑色、黑色。那是什么数字？(8)。
What's the eighth letter in the alphabet? (H). Hold that in your head.
字母表上的第八个字母是什么？(H)。记住它。
Off, on, off, off, on. What number's that? (9)
关闭、开启、关闭、关闭、开启。得出什么数字？(9)
What have I said to you Zander? (The word that you said to us is "Hi")  Is it? Do you agree with him? Did we do "Hi"?
Zander，我对你说什么了？（您对我们说的是“嗨”）是吗？你们同意他吗？我们打招呼了吗？
But these are just dots and cards that are on and off, can I really communicate a message to you doing that?
但这些只是开启和关闭的点和卡， 我真的可以通过这种方式，给你们传送一条消息吗？
(yes) Let's see how good you are. Let's see if I can communicate what month I was born in. Are you ready? Off, on, on, off, off.
（是的）让我看看你们有多棒。大家看看我能不能表示 我在哪个月份出生。准备好了吗？关闭、开启、开启、关闭、关闭。
What month was I born in? Whisper it to me, so many people know the answer, go. (December) You're right.
我在哪个月份出生？轻声告诉我，所以有很多人知道答案。 开始。（十二月）答对了。
So using binary digits and using these dots we can communicate anything from a letter to a number.
因此，我们使用二进制数和使用这些点 就可以传达从字母到数字的任何东西。
You can even do images, you can do sound, you can do movies.
你们甚至还可以用它们表示图像和声音， 还有电影。
Everything involves bits because inside a computer isn't a whole lot of cards like this,
所有涉及位的东西都可以，因为在计算机中， 并没有太多像这样的卡片，
isn't a whole lot of zeros and ones, but it's a whole lot of things that need to be turned on or turned off.
并没有太多的零和一， 但有很多需要开启或关闭的东西。